SULAIMON SAMUEL AYOOLUWA

Creative Designer

Alagbado, Lagos State

+2348067045535

(2)

PROFILE:

DETAILS:

Alagbado, Lagos State, Nigeria.

@sulaimonayooluwa01@gmail.com

SKILLS: •

Graphics Design

Typography

Visual Communications

Brand Management

Print Designs

Color Theory

Strategy

Design Thinking

Interactive Media

First Aid Treatment

o TOOLS: o

Adobe Photoshop CorelDraw Microsoft Office

∘ HOBBIES: ∘

Researching, traveling, Meeting People. Samuel is a creative designer who have adopted the creation of aesthetics and functional designs. I am an enthusiast of designs and an individual who is committed to helping start-ups and brands through the use of compelling designs. My career goal is to take responsibility in whatever environment I am in, adding virtue to such an environment and serving humbly.



EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Creative Designer at Samstar Creations

October 2020 - Till Date

- Brand Identity Designer
- I develop ideas and strategies that show insight and innovation
- I implement the creative execution during the design stages of clients projects.
- I translate creative thinking into imagery and copy that retains and clearly expresses the initial ideas.

Creative Designer at Techtrend Africa

May 2022 - July 2022

- Visual Designer
- I created stunning marketing designs that helped to publicized the brand.
- I led the team of designers in creating designs to sharpen our skills.
- I actively participated in training and business strategy meetings.

Digital Instructor at Graceman I.T. Concept

May 2016 - August 2022

- Creative Designer
- I trained over 50 students on how to operate computer and its application.
- I also trained over 20 students on social media marketing.
- I created wide range of graphics and layouts for beginners with design softwares.
- I reviewed final design layouts and suggesting improvements when and where necessary.

Administrative Secretary at Lagos State Polytechnic, Isolo.

September 2021 - October 2021

- Receptionist/Typist
- I assisted students with typing their final year projects.
- I also managed the office and its environs.

Freelance

October 2020 - Till Date

- General Brand Designer Thobshow Gadgets
- Design Visual content for print and Digital applications that is on-brand, reinforces our status and reputation for brands.
- Designed social media flyers for over 200 brands.
- Managed a campus project for First-City Momentum Bank (FCMB).
- Work autonomously and develop high-quality concepts with minimal instructions.

EDUCATION

B.Sc, Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta.

Nov. 2017 - Nov. 2023

Forestry and Wildlife Management

CERTIFICATE

Certificate of Office (Commandant, Nigerian Red Cross Society) September, 2023

Project Ugrade and Upskill, TUTN

July, 2022

Practical First Aid Training

June, 2020

Basic First Aid Training

April, 2019

Diploma in Desktop Publishing

December, 2018

Lagos State Science and Technology Camp

December, 2012

REFERENCES

References available upon request